A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Field Offices, Paris, RG 6, SG 1 FA395
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Pre-war, 1922-1941; 1; 46 Boxes; 28 cubic feet
  - Pre-war - Correspondence, 01
    - IHD Egypt - Egyptian Account - (La Baule Dossier), 1939 (Box 21, Folder 233)
    - IHD Egypt - Malaria, 1936-1938 (Box 21, Folder 234)
    - IHD Egypt - Malaria, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 235)
    - IHD Egypt - Mediterranean Region - Malaria Research, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 236)
    - IHD Egypt - Schistosomiasis Studies, 1937-1939 (Box 22, Folder 237)
    - IHD Egypt - Schistosomiasis Studies, 1937-1939 (Box 22, Folder 238)
    - IHD Egypt - Sub-Irrigation Study, 1935-1939 (Box 22, Folder 239)
    - IHD England - Bridges, Daisy Caroline - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1937-1939 (Box 22, Folder 240)
    - IHD England - Dobbie-Bateman, Dr. - (Industrial Welfare), 1939 (Box 22, Folder 241)
    - IHD England - Florence Nightingale International Foundation, 1935-1939 (Box 22, Folder 242)
    - IHD England - Florence Nightingale International Foundation - Reports, 1937; 4 items (Box 22, Folder 243)
    - IHD England - Goodman, Neville M. - (Public Health), 1939 (Box 22, Folder 244)
    - IHD England - James, S. P. - (Malaria Research), 1930-1939 (Box 22, Folder 245)
    - IHD England - Kennedy, John Stodart - (Malaria Research), 1938-1939 (Box 22, Folder 246)
    - IHD England - London School of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine, 1933-1939 (Box 23, Folder 247)
    - IHD England - McEwan, Miss - (Nursing), 1933-1939 (Box 23, Folder 248)
    - IHD England - Nabbaro, David - (Syphilis Study), 1939 (Box 23, Folder 249)
    - IHD England - Oxford Nutrition Survey, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 250)
    - IHD England - Papworth Village Settlement - (Tuberculosis), 1936-1939 (Box 23, Folder 251)
    - IHD England - Public Health Nursing, 1922-1939 (Box 23, Folder 252)
    - IHD England - Shortt, Henry E. - (Travel, Medical Parasitology), 1938-1939 (Box 23, Folder 253)
    - IHD England - Abo (Turko) Health Center and Nursing School, 1934-1938 (Box 23, Folder 254)
    - IHD Finland - Helsingfors Demonstration - (Nursing), 1933-1939 (Box 23, Folder 255)
    - IHD Finland - Helsingfors School of Public Health Nursing, 1938-1939 (Box 23, Folder 256)
    - IHD Finland - Institute of Public Health, 1938-1939 (Box 23, Folder 257)
    - IHD Finland - Kansanen, Birgit - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1939 (Box 23, Folder 258)
    - IHD Finland - Lavonius, Herman - (Public Health), 1928-1939 (Box 23, Folder 259)
    - IHD Finland -Leppo, Niilo Erikki Albert - (Fellowship, Pediatrics), 1938-1939 (Box 23, Folder 260)
    - IHD Finland - Luoma, Tyyne - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1931-1939 (Box 23, Folder 261)
    - IHD Finland - Pori (Bjorne Baral) Nursing School and Training Field, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 262)
    - IHD Finland - Public Health Nursing, 1928-1939 (Box 23, Folder 263)
    - IHD Finland - Reinikainen, Oskar - (Travel, Health), 1939 (Box 23, Folder 264)
    - IHD Finland - School for Social Workers, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 265)
    - IHD Finland - Viipuri Nursing School, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 266)
    - IHD France - Bablet, Jean - (Travel, Yellow Fever), 1936-1939 (Box 24, Folder 267)
    - IHD France - Blood Transfusion Institute, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 268)
    - IHD France - Cavillon, J. A. - (Public Health), 1924-1939 (Box 24, Folder 269)
    - IHD France - Comite Francais de Service Social, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 270)
    - IHD France - Hazemann, robert H. - (Pulbic Health), 1939 (Box 24, Folder 271)
    - IHD France - Isaac, Marie - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1937-1939 (Box 24, Folder 272)
    - IHD France - Lyon Nursing School, 1938-1939 (Box 24, Folder 273)
    - IHD France - Paris Institute of Hygiene, 1923-1939 (Box 24, Folder 274)
    - IHD France - Parisot, Jacques - (Public Health), 1923-1939 (Box 24, Folder 275)
    - IHD France - Roubaud, M. E. - (Malariology), 1931-1932, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 276)
    - IHD France - Stefanopoulo, P. J. - (Yellow Fever), 1939 (Box 24, Folder 277)
    - IHD France - Viboral, Lucien - (Travel, Tuberculosis), 1938-1939 (Box 24, Folder 278)
    - IHD Germany - Deposed Scholars, 1933-1938 (Box 24, Folder 279)
      Hecht, Otto - (Medical Entomology) - 1933-1938 Korach, alfred - (Public Health) - 1933-1934 Marx, Norbert - (Medical Statistics) - 1935
    - IHD Germany - Schnitzer, Robert Julius - (Chemotherapy), 1939 (Box 24, Folder 280)
    - IHD Greece - Ambelokipi Health Center, 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 281)
    - IHD Greece - Athens School of Hygiene, 1937-1939 (Box 25, Folder 282)
    - IHD Greece - Athens School of Nursing, 1936-1939 (Box 25, Folder 283)
    - IHD Greece - Hadjinicolaou, J. - (Malariology), 1931-1939 (Box 25, Folder 284)
    - IHD Greece - Livadas, Gregory - (Fellowship, Malariology), 1931-1939 (Box 25, Folder 285)
    - IHD Greece - Malaria Field Demonstration, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 286)
    - IHD Greece - Patrinelli, Helene - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1937-1939 (Box 25, Folder 287)
    - IHD Greece - Rural Health Demonstration, 1931-1938 (Box 25, Folder 288)
    - IHD Greece - Sphangos, Jean - (Pharmacology), 1930-1939 (Box 25, Folder 289)
    - IHD Greece - Zaphiriou, Iphigenia - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1939 (Box 25, Folder 290)
    - IHD Hungary - Benyo, Andrew - (Travel, Child Health), 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 291)
    - IHD Hungary - Berettyoujfalu Health Demonstration, 1930-1935 (Box 25, Folder 292)
    - IHD Hungary - Budapest Institute of Hygiene, 1937-1939 (Box 26, Folder 293)
    - IHD Hungary - Budapest Institute of Hygiene, 1937-1939 (Box 26, Folder 294)
    - IHD Hungary - Budapest School of Nursing, 1934-1939 (Box 26, Folder 295)
    - IHD Hungary - Bureau of Public Health Nursing, 1927-1935 (Box 26, Folder 296)
    - IHD Hungary - Gaal, Andrew - (Public Health), 1924-1939 (Box 26, Folder 297)
    - IHD Hungary - Debrecen Nursing School, 1930-1936 (Box 26, Folder 298)
    - IHD Hungary - Floderer, Istvan - (Fellowship, Industrial Hygiene), 1938-1939 (Box 26, Folder 299)
    - IHD Hungary - Godollo Health Demonstration, 1929-1935 (Box 26, Folder 300)
    - IHD Hungary - Hepp-Bajan, Erno - (Travel, Child Welfare), 1931-1939 (Box 26, Folder 301)
    - IHD Hungary - Hevizy, Tivador - (Public Health), 1934-1937 (Box 26, Folder 302)
    - IHD Hungary - Influenza Study, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 303)
    - IHD Hungary - Influenza Study, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 304)
    - IHD Hungary - Pecs Health Demonstration, 1928-1938 (Box 26, Folder 305)
    - IHD Hungary, 1922-1940 (Box 27, Folder 306)
      Public Health - 1922-1940 Public Health Survey - 1936-1938 Rural Nursing Work - 1933-1936 State Institute of Hygiene - Influenza Study - 1939-1940 Stellar, Maria - (Nursing) - 1931-1939 Szeged Nursing School - 1937-1939 Typhoid Field Research - 1933-1939 Vac Health Demonstration - 1937
    - IHD India - All-India Institute of Hygiene - Calcultta, 1933-1939 (Box 27, Folder 307)
    - IHD India - Chakravarty, Jiten - (Rural Health Work), 1939 (Box 27, Folder 308)
    - IHD India - Chaudhuri, Rabindra Nath - (Fellowship, Tuberculosis), 1938-1939 (Box 27, Folder 309)
    - IHD India - Dharmendra, Dr. - (Fellowship, Bacteriology), 1937-1938 (Box 27, Folder 310)
    - IHD India - Lal, Sardam - (Fellowship, Bacteriology), 1939 (Box 27, Folder 311)
    - IHD India - Mathis, Maurice - (Yellow Fever), 1931, 1938-1939 (Box 27, Folder 312)
    - IHD India - Mathur, W. C. - (Public Health), 1939 (Box 27, Folder 313)
    - IHD India - Menon, M. K. Krishna - (Fellowship, Bacteriology and Immunology), 1938-1939 (Box 27, Folder 314)
    - IHD India - Orkney, Jean M. - (Fellowship, Maternal and Child Health), 1938-1939 (Box 27, Folder 315)
    - IHD India - Rajagopal, Krishna Rao - (Fellowship, Biochemistry), 1938-1939 (Box 27, Folder 316)
    - IHD India - Shah, syed Riaz Ali - (Fellowship, Tuberculosis), 1938-1939 (Box 27, Folder 317)
    - IHD India - Sokhey, S. S. - (Fellowship, Biochemistry), 1924-1925, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 318)
    - IHD Italy - Biocca, Ettore - (IRC Fellowship, Virology), 1939 (Box 27, Folder 319)
    - IHD Italy - Canaperia, Giovanni Alberto - (Fellowship, Epidemiology and Statistics), 1933-1938 (Box 27, Folder 320)
    - IHD Italy - Cattaneo, Carlo - (Fellowship, Pulmonary Diseases), 1938 (Box 27, Folder 321)
    - IHD Italy - Camarossa, Saldino - (Travel, Public Health Administration), 1936-1939 (Box 27, Folder 322)
    - IHD Italy - Daddi, Guiseppi - (Pulmonary Diseases), 1938 (Box 27, Folder 323)
    - IHD Italy - Deposed Scholars, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 324)
    - IHD Italy - Delvecchio, Gaetano - (Public Health), 1938-1939 (Box 27, Folder 325)
    - IHD Italy - Foggia Health Center, 1936-1939 (Box 27, Folder 326)
    - IHD Italy - Laboratory of Malaria Studies, 1937-1939 (Box 28, Folder 327)
    - IHD Italy - Malaria Research - Balkans, Italy and Northern Europe, 1938-1939 (Box 28, Folder 328)
    - IHD Italy - Malaria Research - Balkans, Italy and Northern Europe, 1938-1939 (Box 28, Folder 329)
    - IHD Italy - Mercuri, Dhalma - (Nursing), 1934-1939 (Box 28, Folder 330)
    - IHD Italy - Missiroli, Alberto - (Public Health, Malaria), 1925-1939 (Box 28, Folder 331)
    - IHD Italy - Missiroli, Alberto - (Public Health, Malaria), 1925-1939 (Box 28, Folder 332)
    - IHD Italy - Petragnani, Giovanni - (Travel, Health), 1935-1939 (Box 28, Folder 333)
    - IHD Italy - Revista Di Malariologia, 1938-1939 (Box 28, Folder 334)
    - IHD Italy - Rome Institute of Hygiene, 1934-1939 (Box 29, Folder 335)
    - IHD Italy - Rome Institute of Hygiene, 1934-1939 (Box 29, Folder 336)
    - IHD Italy - Rome Health Center, 1934-1939 (Box 29, Folder 337)
    - IHD Italy - Rome Office Accounts, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 338)
    - IHD Japan - Matouke, Syukiti - (Fellowship, Public Health), 1938-1939 (Box 29, Folder 339)
    - IHD Japan - Yoshioka, Hiroto - (Public Health), 1939 (Box 29, Folder 340)
    - IHD Java - Dinger, Johannes Ernst - (Travel, Hygiene), 1938-1939 (Box 29, Folder 341)
    - IHD Yugoslavia - Borcic, Dr., 1936-1939 (Box 29, Folder 342)
    - IHD Yugoslavia - Central Epidemiological Institute, 1924-1925 (Box 29, Folder 343)
    - IHD Yugoslavia - Malaria, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 344)
    - IHD Yugoslavia - Stampar, A. - (Public Health Administration), 1934-1939 (Box 29, Folder 345)
    - IHD Yugoslavia - Zagreb School of Nursing, 1932-1935, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 346)
    - IHD Yugoslavia - Zagreb School of Nursing, 1932-1935, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 347)
    - IHD Yugoslavia - Zagreb School of Public Health, 1932-1939 (Box 30, Folder 349)
    - IHD Yugoslavia - Zagreb School of Nursing, 1938-1939 (Box 30, Folder 348)
    - IHD Yugoslavia - Zagreb School of Public Health, 1932-1939 (Box 30, Folder 350)
    - IHD Yugoslavia - Zagreb School of Public Health, 1932-1939 (Box 30, Folder 351)
    - IHD Yugoslavia - Zagreb School of Public Health, 1932-1939 (Box 30, Folder 352)
    - IHD Yugoslavia - Zelenjak, Danitza - (Nursing), 1925-1939 (Box 30, Folder 353)
    - IHD Lithuania - Red Cross Nursing School, 1939 (Box 30, Folder 354)
    - IHD Mexico - Bustos-C, Jose - (Maternal and Child Health), 1939 (Box 30, Folder 355)
    - IHD Mexico - Manquez-E, Manuel B. - (Fellow, Hygiene), 1939 (Box 30, Folder 356)
    - IHD New Zealand - Cameron, Flora J. - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1938-1939 (Box 30, Folder 357)
    - IHD New Zealand - Watt, Michael H. - (Travel, Public Health), 1938-1939 (Box 30, Folder 358)
    - IHD Norway - Epidemiological and Dagnostic Laboratory for Most Northern Provinces, 1938-1939 (Box 30, Folder 359)
    - IHD Norway - Gaustad, Victor - (Fellowship, Bacteriology), 1936-1939 (Box 30, Folder 360)
    - IHD Norway - Public Health Nursing School, 1929-1930 (Box 30, Folder 361)
    - IHD Norway - Palestine - Animals - (Shipment of Hamsters), 1939 (Box 30, Folder 362)
    - IHD Poland - Cracow School of Nursing, 1924-1931 (Box 30, Folder 363)
    - IHD Poland - Cracow School of Nursing, 1932-1938 (Box 31, Folder 364)
    - IHD Poland - Cracow School of Nursing, 1932-1938 (Box 31, Folder 365)
    - IHD Poland - Fellowship Procedure, 1926-1938 (Box 31, Folder 366)
    - IHD Poland - Grezgorewski, Edward - (Fellowship, Public Health and Vital Statistics), 1932-1939 (Box 31, Folder 367)
    - IHD Poland - Jakubowski, Marian - (Social Insurance), 1939 (Box 31, Folder 368)
    - IHD Poland - Mirkowski, W. - (Appled Serology), 1939 (Box 31, Folder 369)
    - IHD Poland - Orzechowska, Stanislava - (Travel, Nursing), 1938-1939 (Box 31, Folder 370)
    - IHD Poland - Public Health, 1926-1940 (Box 31, Folder 371)
    - IHD Poland - Public Health Education Propaganda, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 372)
    - IHD Poland - Public Health Nursing, 1922-1926 (Box 31, Folder 373)
    - IHD Poland - Public Health Nursing, 1937 (Box 31, Folder 374)
    - IHD Poland - Social Welfare and Health Program, 1932-1934 (Box 31, Folder 375)
    - IHD Poland - State Department of Health - Bureau of Public Health Nursing, 1926-1936 (Box 31, Folder 376)
    - IHD Poland - State Department of Health - Bureau of District Health Work, 1927-1936 (Box 31, Folder 377)
    - IHD Poland - State Institute and School of Hygiene, 1932-1935 (Box 31, Folder 378)
    - IHD Poland - Typhus Vaccine Study, 1936-1939 (Box 31, Folder 379)
    - IHD Poland - Warsaw Institute of Mental Hygiene, 1934-1938 (Box 31, Folder 380)
    - IHD Poland - Warsaw School of Nursing, 1922-1932 (Box 31, Folder 381)
    - IHD Poland - Zelechowska, Anna - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1938-1939 (Box 31, Folder 382)
    - IHD Portugal - Angola Colony, 1939 (Box 31, Folder 383)
    - IHD Portugal - Bastos, Maria Angelica de Lima - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1935-1939 (Box 31, Folder 384)
    - IHD Portugal - Braz, Maria Margarida Spencer Moura - (Nursing), 1939 (Box 32, Folder 385)
    - IHD Portugal - Coimbra Health Demonstration, 1937-1939 (Box 32, Folder 386)
    - IHD Portugal - Coimbra School of Nursing, 1938-1939 (Box 32, Folder 387)
    - IHD Portugal - da Silva Araujo, Ferninando Nunez - (Fellowship, Epidemiology), 1933-1939 (Box 32, Folder 388)
    - IHD Portugal - de Lemos, Maria Conceicao Viana - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1936-1939 (Box 32, Folder 389)
    - IHD Portugal - de Moraes, Maria Palmira Tito - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1936-1939 (Box 32, Folder 390)
    - IHD Portugal - Epidemiological Laboratory, 1937-1938 (Box 32, Folder 391)
    - IHD Portugal - Lisbon Cancer Institute Nursing School, 1936-1939 (Box 32, Folder 392)
    - IHD Portugal - Lisbon Health Center, 1934-1939 (Box 32, Folder 393)
    - IHD Portugal - Lisbon Institute of Hygiene, 1934-1939 (Box 32, Folder 394)
    - IHD Portugal - Lisbon Model Health Center, 1939-1940 (Box 32, Folder 395)
    - IHD Portugal - Lisbon School of Nursing, 1934-1939 (Box 32, Folder 396)
    - IHD Portugal - Malaria, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 397)
    - IHD Portugal - Public Health, 1931-1938 (Box 32, Folder 398)
    - IHD Portugal - Public Health Demonstrations and Health Centers, 1935-1939 (Box 32, Folder 399)
    - IHD Portugal - Public Health Nursing, 1937, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 400)
    - IHD Portugal - Tedeschi, Helena de Mello - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1937-1939 (Box 33, Folder 401)
    - IHD Portugal - Teves, Maria Lomelina, 1938-1939 (Box 33, Folder 402)
    - IHD Roumania - Bucharest Health Center, 1938-1939 (Box 33, Folder 403)
    - IHD Roumania - Bucharest Health Center, 1938-1939 (Box 33, Folder 404)
    - IHD Roumania - Bucharest Institute of Hygiene, 1937-1939 (Box 33, Folder 405)
    - IHD Roumania - Bucharest School of Nursing, 1937-1939 (Box 33, Folder 406)
    - IHD Roumania - Bucharest School of Nursing, 1937-1939 (Box 33, Folder 407)
    - IHD Roumania - Combiescu, Dimitri - (Fellowship, Experimental Medicine and Public Health Administration), 1921-1939 (Box 33, Folder 408)
    - IHD Roumania - Dornescu, Adrian - (Travel, Public Health), 1939 (Box 33, Folder 409)
    - IHD Roumania - Dmitrescu, Aureliu - (Travel, Public Health), 1939 (Box 33, Folder 410)
    - IHD Roumania - Ionescu, Alexandrina - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1936-1938 (Box 33, Folder 411)
    - IHD Roumania - Lustrea, Vasile - (Mental Hygiene), 1936-1939 (Box 34, Folder 412)
    - IHD Roumania - Manuila, Sabin - (Public Health Administration), 1928-1939 (Box 34, Folder 413)
    - IHD Roumania - Marinescu, Nicolas - (Travel, Hygiene), 1939 (Box 34, Folder 414)
    - IHD Roumania - Public Health, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 415)
    - IHD Roumania - Public Health Demonstrations, 1927-1939 (Box 34, Folder 416)
    - IHD Roumania - Scarlet Fever Study, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 417)
    - IHD Roumania - Naum, George - (Travel, Public Health), 1939 (Box 34, Folder 418)
    - IHD Russia - Toumanoff, Constantin - (IEB Fellowship, Immunology), 1925-1927, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 419)
    - IHD Spain - Deposed Scholars, 1936-1939 (Box 34, Folder 420)
    - IHD Spain - Malaria Field Investigations, 1936-1939 (Box 34, Folder 421)
    - IHD Spain - Public Health, 1926-1938 (Box 34, Folder 422)
    - IHD Spain - Public Health Nursing, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 423)
    - IHD Spain - Smallpox Vaccine Laboratory, 1934-1939 (Box 34, Folder 424)
    - IHD Spain - Smallpox Vaccine Laboratory, 1934-1939 (Box 34, Folder 425)
    - IHD Spain - Smallpox Vaccine Laboratory, 1934-1939 (Box 34, Folder 426)
    - IHD Spain - Vallecas Health Center, 1931-1939 (Box 35, Folder 427)
    - IHD Spain - Zozaya, Carlos - (Study Trip, Tropical Pathology), 1932-1939 (Box 35, Folder 428)
    - IHD Sweden - Field Training and Demonstration Service, 1938-1939 (Box 35, Folder 429)
    - IHD Sweden - Gard, Sven - (Fellowship, Bacteriology), 1938-1939 (Box 35, Folder 430)
    - IHD Sweden - Gave, Eric - (Travel, Public Health), 1938-1939 (Box 35, Folder 431)
    - IHD Sweden - Hojer, Axel - (Travel, Public Health), 1939 (Box 35, Folder 432)
    - IHD Sweden - Hojer, Gerda - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1938-1939 (Box 35, Folder 433)
    - IHD Sweden - Institute of Hygiene, 1932-1939 (Box 35, Folder 434)
    - IHD Sweden - Institute of Hygiene, 1932-1939 (Box 35, Folder 435)
    - IHD Sweden - Institute of Hygiene - Report, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 436)
    - IHD Sweden - Naesland, Carl Albert - (Travel, Public Health), 1938-1939 (Box 35, Folder 437)
    - IHD Sweden - Public Health, 1923-1939 (Box 35, Folder 438)
    - IHD Sweden - Public Health Nursing, 1930-1939 (Box 35, Folder 439)
    - IHD Sweden - Reitz, Einar - (Travel, Health), 1939 (Box 35, Folder 440)
    - IHD Sweden - Tiselius, Arne Wilhelm Kauren - (Travel, Biochemistry), 1939 (Box 35, Folder 441)
    - IHD Sweden - Tjellstrom, Hildur Maja Elisabeth - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1939 (Box 35, Folder 442)
    - IHD Turkey - Ankara Institute of Hygiene, 1934-1939 (Box 36, Folder 443)
    - IHD Turkey - Ankara Institute of Hygiene, 1934-1939 (Box 36, Folder 444)
    - IHD Turkey - Ankara Institute of Hygiene, 1934-1939 (Box 36, Folder 445)
    - IHD Turkey - Ankara Health Center, 1935-1939 (Box 36, Folder 446)
    - IHD Turkey - Ankara State School of Nursing, 1928-1939 (Box 36, Folder 447)
    - IHD Turkey - Serum Farm, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 448)
    - IHD Turkey - Bilginer, Tarik - (Fellowship, Public Health Engineering), 1939 (Box 36, Folder 449)
    - IHD Turkey - Eneren, Tomric - (Nursing), 1938-1939 (Box 36, Folder 450)
    - IHD Turkey - Health Center, Edirnekapou, 1934-1939 (Box 36, Folder 451)
    - IHD Turkey - Health Center, Edirnekapou, 1934-1939 (Box 36, Folder 452)
    - IHD Turkey - Health Centers, 1938 (Box 36, Folder 453)
    - IHD Turkey - Idil, Kamil - (Formerly Bilol Kiamil-Mumtaz Bey) - (Fellowship, Epidemiology), 1929-1939 (Box 37, Folder 454)
    - IHD Turkey - Kiper, Cemal Ali - (Fellowship, Industrial Hygiene), 1939 (Box 37, Folder 455)
    - IHD Turkey - Olcer, Memduh - (Fellowship, Sanitary Engineering), 1937-1939 (Box 37, Folder 456)
    - IHD Turkey - Red Crescent Nursing School, 1923-1939 (Box 37, Folder 457)
    - IHD Turkey - Refik, Bey - (Public Health), 1924-1937 (Box 37, Folder 458)
      Includes Gunn, S. M., "Diary of Visit to Turkey", May 1925
    - IHD Turkey - Turer, Asumen - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1938-1939 (Box 37, Folder 459)
    - IHD Turkey - Tumerkam, Muhit - (Fellowship, Hygiene), 1939 (Box 37, Folder 460)
    - IHD Turkey - Chayer, Mary Ellis - (Travel, Nursing), 1939 (Box 37, Folder 461)
    - IHD League of Nations - Eastern Bureau, 1924-1931 (Box 37, Folder 462)
    - IHD League of Nations - Financial, 1934-1939 (Box 37, Folder 463)
    - IHD League of Nations - Financial, 1934-1939 (Box 37, Folder 464)
    - IHD League of Nations - Health Section - Miscellaneous, 1929-1939 (Box 38, Folder 465)
    - IHD League of Nations - International School of Advanced Health Studies, 1930-1939 (Box 38, Folder 466)
    - IHD League of Nations - Malaria Commission, 1929-1939 (Box 38, Folder 467)
    - IHD League of Nations - Permanent Standardization Commission, 1934-1938 (Box 38, Folder 468)
    - IHD League of Nations - Rajchman, Ludwig - (Director, Health Section), 1924-1939 (Box 38, Folder 469)
    - IHD League of Nations - Schistosomiasis Study, 1938-1939 (Box 38, Folder 470)
    - IHD League of Nations - Schools of Hygiene, 1930-1938 (Box 38, Folder 471)
    - IHD General - Correspondence Asknowledgements, 1939 (Box 38, Folder 472)
    - IHD General - Emergency Program, 1939 (Box 38, Folder 473)
    - IHD General - Fellowship Procedure, 1937-1939 (Box 38, Folder 474)
    - IHD General - Field Staff, 1924-1939 (Box 38, Folder 475)
    - IHD General - Laboratory Animals Fund, 1938-1939 (Box 38, Folder 476)
    - IHD General - Literature Fund, 1939 (Box 38, Folder 477)
    - IHD General - Malaria Research and Control Demonstration in Mediterranean Region, 1939 (Box 38, Folder 478)
    - IHD General - Procedure and Financial, 1937-1939 (Box 38, Folder 479)
    - IHD General - Public Health Nursing, 1929, 1937-1939 (Box 39, Folder 480)
    - IHD General - Rabies, 1936-1939 (Box 39, Folder 481)
    - IHD General - Rockefeller Institute, 1935 (Box 39, Folder 482)
    - IHD General - Rockefeller Institute, 1936-1939 (Box 39, Folder 483)
    - IHD General - Schools of Nursing - Procedure, 1927-1938 (Box 39, Folder 484)
    - IHD General - Study of European Institutes of Hygiene, 1939 (Box 39, Folder 485)
    - IHD General - Syphilis Study, 1938-1939 (Box 39, Folder 486)
    - IHD General - Travel of Visiting Health Officials and Training of Health Workers, 1924-1928 (Box 39, Folder 487)
    - IHD General - Travel of Visiting Health Officials and Training of Health Workers, 1929-1938 (Box 39, Folder 488)
    - IHD General - Travel of Visiting Health Officials and Training of Health Workers, 1929-1938 (Box 39, Folder 489)
    - IHD General - Yellow Fever Cooperation with Office International Hygiene Publique, 1934-1939 (Box 39, Folder 490)
    - SS Project Memoranda and Correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box 40, Folder 491)
      Kittredge, Tracy B. to New York - 1939-1940 Draft of Memorandum on Refugee Scholars - January 23, 1940
    - SS Project Memoranda and Correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box 40, Folder 492)
    - General China Program, 1937-1940 (Box 40, Folder 493)
      Agricultural Economics - Nanking University - 1937-1938 Commission on Medical Education - 1938 Hsing-ya Medical College - 1940 Nankai Institute of Economics - 1939 National Central University - 1938 National Council for Rural Reconstruction - 1938-1939 Yen, James C. - 1940
    - General Cite Universitaire - (General Support and International House), 1926-1940 (Box 40, Folder 494)
    - General Cite Universitaire - (General Support and International House), 1926-1940 (Box 40, Folder 495)
  - Pre-war - Financial Material, 02
    - Commission for the Prevention of Tuberculosis in France, 1917-1922 (Box 41, Folder 496)
      Audit Reports - (6) - 1917-1922 Salary Increases - 1919-1920
    - International Education Board - Audit Reports, 1926-1927; 2 items (Box 41, Folder 497)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - Audit Reports, 1923-1929; 8 items (Box 41, Folder 498)